(
"ai_sub_version": "1.9.1",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 2,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"subtitles": 8
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": false,
"scrub": true
)
あー 見てんの？ Yeah!
Ah, you're watching? Yeah!
1, 2, 3 でねぇし
1, 2, and not 3
犬神ドクミツ ドギドギゴースト無視
Inugami Dokumitsu, ignore Doggy Doggy Ghost
ころねや キレてるね かなりハード
Korone is cutting loose, quite hard
みんなの竹取ジコロさん
Everyone's Taketori Jicoro-san
ここ見てるころね クリーミーモモ
Watching here, Korone, Creamy Momo
みんなもっともっと ドギもっと暴れ
Everyone more and more, go doggy-wild more
ほら おっぽ振って 好気系 ろっくすたー
Look, wag your tail, aerobic rockstar
調子いいね 泡のシーン
Feeling good, the bubble scene
はい準備 Seesaw Game 探すよ Ghost
Ready, Seesaw Game, searching for the Ghost
宙空(そら)へと飛ばす 一切 かまわない Step
Flying to the sky, steps that don't mind a thing
空まで昇れ だから
Rise to the sky, so...
ゴチゴチ君に 優しくポイ飛ばす
Strictly to you, gently tossing away
熱中症入る ねぇねぇころね Oh Yeah!
Heatstroke kicks in, hey hey Korone Oh Yeah!
テラノマウェイ (Hey! Hey! Awoo!)
Terranomaway (Hey! Hey! Awoo!)
ワスカバピョエ Oh Yeah!
Waskabapyoe Oh Yeah!
シラノパリー (Hey! Hey! Awoo!)
Siranoparree (Hey! Hey! Awoo!)
おりこうはギャップ
The clever one's gap
ワンワンワン！ ダダダ！ ワンチャンりのままさん
Woof woof woof! Dadada! One chance, Rino-mama-san
ワンワンワン！ ダダダ！ 船子の機長さん
Woof woof woof! Dadada! Funako's captain
飛んだら離さない ワンチャン隅まで輝く
Won't let go once I fly, one chance to shine everywhere
君に絶対 大好き
I absolutely love you
レギュラーじゃ堪らない ドキドキ
Can't stand being regular, heart pounding
汗かき 炸(さっ)かき 健気計画
Sweating, exploding, brave plan
天下で電通 惑星脱出
Dentsu in the world, planet escape
みんなのヴィーソーに ぺろぺろ ぺろぺろ
Lick lick lick on everyone's visor
畜生殻から みんな見頃の
From the animal shell, everyone's at their peak
録画は間近な パない逆転の金歯
Recording is near, insane turnaround with a gold tooth
激熱 Bring it my bow wow
Super hot, bring it my bow wow
鼻歌 旗揚げ ハイパーのよっしゃー
Humming, raising the flag, hyper 'yessir'
脳内傘刺して 漏らすよ だから
Sticking an umbrella in the brain, it's leaking, so...
空まで昇れ だから
Rise to the sky, so...
ゴチゴチ君に 鍵のよす飛ばす
Strictly to you, throwing keys
熱中症入り ねぇねぇころね Oh Yeah!
Heatstroke kicks in, hey hey Korone Oh Yeah!
テラノマウェイ (Hey! Hey! Awoo!)
Terranomaway (Hey! Hey! Awoo!)
ワスカバピョエ Oh Yeah!
Waskabapyoe Oh Yeah!
シラノパリー (Hey! Hey! Awoo!)
Siranoparree (Hey! Hey! Awoo!)
おりこうはギャップ
The clever one's gap
ワンワンワン！ ダダダ！ ワンチャンりのままさん
Woof woof woof! Dadada! One chance, Rino-mama-san
ワンワンワン！ ダダダ！ 船子の機長さん
Woof woof woof! Dadada! Funako's captain
飛んだら離さない ワンチャン隅まで輝く
Won't let go once I fly, one chance to shine everywhere
君に絶対 大好き
I absolutely love you
レギュラーじゃ堪らない ドキドキ
Can't stand being regular, heart pounding
おーらい！ 鎖に繋がれるなんて真っ平ごめんあそばせ
Alright! I beg your pardon, but I refuse to be chained
ちょーハイパツで時期なごとく 進化バイブスが満ちちゃう
With super high spirits, the evolution vibes are overflowed
ドギーとドギー 噛みつき ドギー
Doggy and Doggy, biting Doggy
Feel so final ノリノリノリノリ
Feel so final, groove groove groove groove
一切合切 お邪魔させ ドギドギガイ
Everything altogether, let me interrupt, Doggy Doggy Guy
You can go Bye Bye ばーべ ドギドギガイ
You can go Bye Bye babe, Doggy Doggy Guy
当然 邪魔していいほどに ドギドギガイ
Of course, to the point it's okay to interrupt, Doggy Doggy Guy
Clap your hands! 上げて飛ばそう ノリノリノリノリ
Clap your hands! Lift them up and fly, groove groove groove groove
ワンワンワン！ ダダダ！ ワンチャンりのままさん
Woof woof woof! Dadada! One chance, Rino-mama-san
ワンワンワン！ ダダダ！ 船子の機長さん
Woof woof woof! Dadada! Funako's captain
飛んだら離さない ワンチャン隅まで輝く
Won't let go once I fly, one chance to shine everywhere
君に絶対 大好き
I absolutely love you
レギュラーじゃ堪らない ドキドキ
Can't stand being regular, heart pounding
あれ？あれ？
Huh? Huh?
ころちゃん遅いな。
Koro-chan is late.
これどうしようかな、これ？
What should I do about this?
あれ？みんな、始まってるこれ？
Huh? Everyone, is it starting?
やべっやべっ！かなすぎこれ！
Oh no, oh no! It's too much!
パラパラ上がってるよこれ！
It's fluttering up!
これパラパラ具合か！
Is it the flutter condition?!
パラパラ具合か！パラ具合…
The flutter condition! Para-condition...
そりゃ！よいしょ！
There! Heave-ho!
いやパラ具合させてる場合じゃねえ！どこだ？
Wait, this is no time for para-conditions! Where is she?
あ、ごめんごめん！
Ah, sorry, sorry!
ころちゃん！やっと来てくれたよ！
Koro-chan! You're finally here!
みんなお待たせ！お待たせだよ本当に！
Everyone, sorry to keep you waiting! Really!
待って待って！はあ、はあ…
Wait, wait! *panting*
落ち着いて！息、息整えて！
Calm down! Catch your breath!
いやころちゃん来ないからびっくりしちゃってさ！
I was surprised because you didn't come, Koro-chan!
チョコチョコ始まっちゃうのかなと思ってさ！
I thought it might start little by little!
待ってね！待って！はあ、はあ、はあ…
Wait! Wait! *heavy panting*
ちょっとすごいね！
That's quite something!
一回止めよっか？大丈夫？
Should we stop for a second? Are you okay?
水、水持ってくる？大丈夫？運動不足だね！
Water, should I get some water? You okay? You're out of shape!
そうだね…
Yeah...
ということでお待たせ！
Anyway, sorry for the wait!
いきなり寝てやるっつってもびっくりしちゃったよ！
I was surprised even though you said you'd suddenly 'lie down'!
ちょっとね、間がちょっと怖くてさ！
You see, the silence was a bit scary!
あーそうなんだ、ごめんね！遅くなったね！
Ah, I see, sorry! I was late!
いいよいいよ、ありがとう！
It's okay, thank you!
じゃあ始めてもいいかい？
Well, can we start?
オッケー、始めましょう！
Okay, let's start!
いくぞ！早速始めるよー！
Let's go! Let's start right away!
ハッチポッチステーション
Hotch Potch Station
ハッチポッチステーション うーうーうー
Hotch Potch Station ooh-ooh-ooh
何でもありの
Anything goes
楽しい駅
at this fun station
楽しい仲間
Fun friends
めったに電車は来ないけど
Trains rarely come here, but
さあおいで
Come on over
（ジャーニー）
(Journey)
みんなで一緒に
Everyone together
（グッチ）
(Gucci)
楽しく遊ぼう
Let's have fun playing
（ダイヤ）
(Dia)
ハッチポッチ
Hotch Potch
パーティータイム
Party time
ハッチポッチステーション
Hotch Potch Station
ハッチポッチステーション うーうーうー
Hotch Potch Station ooh-ooh-ooh
ハッチポッチショップの
At the Hotch Potch Shop
ダイヤさん
is Dia-san
（はい！）
(Yes!)
キュートでワイルド
Cute and wild
たまには喧嘩もするけれど
Sometimes we fight, but
ほんとはやさしい
actually she's kind
（そうね）
(That's right)
世界の恋人
The world's sweetheart
（んふん）
(Mhmm)
ニコニコ元気に
Always smiling and healthy
ハッチポッチ
Hotch Potch
ファミリー
Family
改札口の
At the ticket gate
ジャーニー君
is Journey-kun
（なりよ！）
(Nari-yo!)
せっかちどんかち
Hasty and stubborn
たまには遅刻もするけれど
Sometimes he's late, but
ほんとはまじめな
actually he's serious
（そうそう）
(Yes, yes)
お人好し
Good-natured
（よいしょっと）
(Heave-ho)
ワイワイ楽しい
Lively and fun
ハッチポッチ
Hotch Potch
ファミリー
Family
とってもおしゃれ
Very fashionable
エチケットじいさん
Etiquette Jiisan
（チケットやで！）
(It's Ticket!)
いつでも元気
Always energetic
説教どこでも始まるけれど
His lectures start everywhere, but
下から読んでも
Whether you read from the bottom
（なんやろう）
(I wonder what)
上から読んでも
or from the top
（パッチポッチ）
(Patch Potch)
じいさん天才児
Jiisan is a genius child
ハッチポッチ
Hotch Potch
ファミリー
Family
ハッチポッチ、ハッチポッチ
Hotch Potch, Hotch Potch
はーっ…
Haaa...
ハッ、ハッ、ハッ、ハッ
Ha, ha, ha, ha
ハッチポッチステーション
Hotch Potch Station
（テンション）
(Tension)
ハッ、ハッ、ハッ、ハッ、ハッ
Ha, ha, ha, ha, ha
ハッチポッチ、ハッチポッチ
Hotch Potch, Hotch Potch
ハッチポッチステーション
Hotch Potch Station
ハッチポッチステーション うーうーうー
Hotch Potch Station ooh-ooh-ooh
うすべったい
Thin and flat
トランクちゃん
Trunk-chan
ミラクルマジック
Miracle magic
いつでもワンワン吠えてるけれど
Always barking 'woof woof', but
みんなの気持ちは ちゃんとわかってる
she understands everyone's feelings
かわいい仲間
A cute friend
ハッチポッチ
Hotch Potch
ファミリー
Family
お調子者の
The frivolous
グッチさん
Gucci-san
（よっしゃー！）
(Alright!)
ギラギラスターを
The glittering stars
ロマンティックに夢見て
dreaming about them romantically
歌って踊れば
When he sings and dances
誰でも笑っちゃう
everyone ends up laughing
みんな大好き
Everyone loves him
ハッチポッチ
Hotch Potch
ファミリー
Family
ハッチポッチステーション
Hotch Potch Station
バーン！
Bam!
イエーーーイ！！
Yay!!!
いいえ！いいスタートが切れたんじゃないの？
No! Wasn't that a great start?
本当だよ、そうだよね、本当に。ねえ、うん。
That's true, it really was, honestly. Right? Yeah.
いいスタートが切れたんじゃないの？
Wasn't that a great start?
いいスタート、いいスタート、いいスタート、それ！
Good start, good start, good start, there!
ぼーっとしてた。ここ、いいスタート、いやぁ！
I was spaced out. Here, a good start, yeah!
すごいすごい、初めて見た！
Wow, wow, first time seeing that!
ぼーっとしてたよ！さっきも見たさっきも見た。
I was spaced out! I saw it just now too.
いやぁ、いい曲聴いたらぼーっとしてたよ、本当にね。
Yeah, listening to a good song made me space out, really.
ありがとうね。
Thanks.
いいよ、全然いいよ、うん。
It's okay, totally fine, yeah.
結局外すね。これ外す...
I'll take it off in the end. Taking this off...
これ外す。ああ、それ偽物なの？それ。
Taking this off. Ah, is that a fake?
偽物じゃない、これアンジェリーナ。
It's not a fake, this is Angelina.
あ、可愛いね。ちょっと似てるな、何かここ。
Oh, how cute. It looks a bit like you.
似てないよ、世界観が似てない似てない。
It doesn't. The world views don't match at all.
いやいやいや、ということで、ころちゃん！
No no no, anyway, Koro-chan!
はい！
Yes!
初めましてだね、これね。
This is our first time meeting, right?
初めましてだよ、ゴー☆ジャスさんは。
It is our first time! Gorgeous-san is...
あ、ちょっと...え？ちょっと水臭いな。ゴー☆ジャスでいいよ。
Wait... eh? That's a bit distant. Just Gorgeous is fine.
え、ゴー☆ジャスでいいの？
Eh, just Gorgeous is fine?
いい全然。お前らはゴー☆ジャスさんってつけろよ！
It's fine. You guys better call me Gorgeous-san!
あ、ころだけ特別ね。
Ah, so only Korone is special.
あ、じゃあゴー☆ジャスはさ、芸歴何年なの？
So Gorgeous, how many years have you been in show business?
芸歴ね、恥ずかしいんだけどね、25年やってるね。
My career length, it's a bit embarrassing, but I've been doing it for 25 years.
大先輩やないかい！
You're a huge senior!
でもずっと売れてないから全然...まだ若手で換算してほしい。
But I haven't been popular all this time, so... I want you to still count me as a newcomer.
売れてるよ！
You're popular!
じゃあ、ころと一緒ってことでいい？
Then, can we say you're the same as Korone?
そう？ころちゃんも若手？
Really? Is Koro-chan a newcomer too?
ころ6年目だね。
Korone is in her 6th year.
6年目...あ、尊いぐらいだね。
6th year... oh, that's about precious.
まだ中堅かな？
Still a mid-career, maybe?
まだ中堅...いや、じゃあ同じぐらいだね。このVTuber界とお笑い界みたいな感じだね。
Still mid-career... well then it's about the same level in the VTuber world and comedy world.
ということでございまして...ちょっとそうだ。僕のことやっぱり知らない人いるから、一回本気の自己紹介やっちゃっていい？
And so... wait. There are people who don't know me, so can I do my serious self-introduction once?
あ、そうだね。いいよ。
Oh, right. Go ahead.
一回いきますよ。じゃあいきますよいきますよいきますよ。
Here I go once. Alright, here I go, here I go, here I go.
ワン、ツー！
One, two!
君のハートに、レボ☆リューション！宇宙海賊のゴー☆ジャスです、よろしくお願いします！
Revolution in your heart! I'm the Space Pirate Gorgeous, nice to meet you!
はい！
Yes!
宇宙海賊なんですよ、そうなんですよ。
I'm a Space Pirate, that's right.
あ、そうなの？じゃあ宇宙に住んでるってこと？
Oh, really? So you live in space?
いや目黒区に住んでるけどね。
No, I live in Meguro ward though.
目黒区なんだ、言っていいのそれ？
You live in Meguro ward? Is it okay to say that?
もういい全然、うん。ちゃんと住民票出してるから。
It's fine, totally. I've properly filed my residency certificate.
じゃあ芸歴24年の...25年。25年の目黒区の芸人さんね。
So a comedian from Meguro ward with 25 years of career.
まとめないでよ！それぐらいの人も結局目黒区住んでるからね、同じようなね。
Don't summarize it like that! People at that level end up living in Meguro anyway.
あ、ちょっと待って。
Ah, wait a minute.
えっとね、今日ハッシュタグがあってね、犬神ころね6周年ってつけて、みんな呟いてね。
Um, there's a hashtag today. Everyone, please tweet using #InugamiKorone6thAnniversary.
お！これ？出てるよそこね、ここ！ハッシュタグ！
Oh! This? It's showing up there, right here! Hashtag!
ハッシュタグ、ハッシュタグ、それ！ここ！ハッシュタグ！
Hashtag, hashtag, there! Here! Hashtag!
じゃないんだね、その何か国名みたいな...ハッシュタグはないんだ。
It's not that, like your country name gag... There's no hashtag version.
ないよ、ハッシュタグはダメだよ、そこぼやかしちゃうとハッシュタグみんな呟いてくれなくなっちゃうからね。
There isn't. You can't mess with the hashtag or people won't use it.
ないのもあるんだ、できないのもあるんだね。
So there are some things you don't have, things you can't do.
ないときはないからね。しょうがないよね。ということでね。
When I don't have it, I don't. It can't be helped. Anyway...
ちょっとね、何かちょっと二人の距離を縮めたい何かね。
I kind of want to close the distance between us somehow.
あ、何か縮めちゃう？
Oh, should we close it?
うん。何かでもさ、何か今更だけどさ、いつも見てるころちゃんと違う雰囲気なんだけどこれ。
Yeah. But also, it's a bit late to say, but you have a different vibe from the Korone-chan I usually see.
いつもの見た目知ってるの？
Do you know my usual appearance?
知ってるよちゃんと！見てきたよちゃんと事前に。
I know it properly! I checked it out beforehand.
嘘！あんまり変わらないよでも。
Liar! But I don't look that different.
変わらないのこれ？変わらないとは変わらないけどね。
You don't? Well, it's not that different, but...
ちょっと小さくなったぐらいだよね。
...you've just become a bit smaller, right?
Just a bit smaller, right.
現寸がちょっと分からないですけどもね。
I don't know your actual size though.
まあ小さいといえばさ、ゴー☆ジャスはさ、どんな子供だったの？
Speaking of small, Gorgeous, what kind of child were you?
あ、ゴー☆ジャス？ゴー☆ジャスはね、結局田舎の育ちなんだね、うん。
Oh, Gorgeous? Gorgeous grew up in the countryside, you see.
目黒区じゃないんだ。
Not in Meguro ward?
目黒区じゃないんだ。福島県いわき市、うん。
Not Meguro ward. Iwaki City, Fukushima Prefecture.
全然、あのね、もう全然普通に、元々こういう派手なことしようと思ってない子供だったからね。
I was just a completely normal child who didn't plan on doing flashy things like this.
でと普通に虫捕まえてたね、小学校の頃とかはね。
I used to catch bugs normally back in elementary school.
きも！
Gross!
嘘だろおい！虫きも！虫きもって。
No way, hey! "Bugs are gross"? "Bugs are gross"?
え、どんな虫？どんな虫？
Ehh, what kind of bugs? What kind of bugs?
トンボとか...セミとか...ね。みんなそうでしょ？今の公とか違うのかな？
Dragonflies... cicadas... right. Everyone was like that, right? Maybe kids nowadays are different?
あ、そう虫捕り少年はいるよね。少年やってた？
Ah, yeah, there are bug-catching boys. Were you one?
え、ころちゃん虫捕まえたことないの？
Eh, Koro-chan, have you never caught a bug?
いや、ころちゃんはね、小さい時はね、虫大丈夫だったん。セミも捕めたし、大丈夫だったんだけど。
No, when I was little, I was fine with bugs. I could catch cicadas and all, I was fine.
やっぱさ、大人になったらさ、虫きも、ってなったよね。
But once I grew up, I started feeling like "bugs are gross."
うん、虫きも！虫きも！とまずな、それはしょうがないね。
Yeah, bugs are gross! Bugs are gross! Well, that can't be helped.
え、そのさ目の星はさ、いつからできたの？
Hey, that star on your eye, when did you get that?
これは僕がね、あのね、田舎から上京するときにね、あのスーパーひたちっていう常磐線乗ってるときに、あの宇宙人に連れ去られちゃったの。
When I was moving to Tokyo, while I was on the Super Hitachi express on the Joban Line, I was abducted by aliens.
へ！
Huh!
でそれで、あの宇宙人のね、あの色々なあのあれを、施しを受けて、あの宇宙海賊として覚醒したわけよ。
And after receiving various treatments from those aliens, I awakened as a Space Pirate.
そうなんだ。
I see.
そうなんだ。いろいろ、いろいろあって、設定変わっちゃったんだよな。
That's right. Various... various things happened, and my background story changed.
そうなんだ。
Is that so?
そうなんだよ。もう25年やってると、そうだろう。
It is. When you've been doing this for 25 years, that's how it goes.
そっか、そうね。
I guess so.
ん？
Huh?
そっか、そっか。
I see, I see.
これで、これで、なんかもう本当に、ヤッ…！ 焼きんっ！
With this, with this, it's really like, a b-b-burning!
痛いじゃん。根性焼きってことじゃん。
That's painful. You're talking about cigarette burns.
ねえ。
Hey.
ちょっとこれ、今初めて言ったやつだから、あの、Wikiとかに書かないでほしいね。
Hey, I just said that for the first time, so please don't write that on a wiki.
ということで、Wikipediaに書いてください。
So everyone, please write that on Wikipedia.
書くんじゃないよ、これ。
Don't write that down!
うん、そうなんですよね。
Yeah, that's how it is.
もうちょっと喋る？
Shall we talk a bit more?
もうちょっと…ちょっとね僕も、ころちゃんゴー☆ジャスのこと知ってた？
A bit more... I'm curious too, Koro-chan, did you know about Gorgeous?
え、知ってるよ。
Oh, I knew you.
何で見たことある？
Where have you seen me?
え、わかんないけど、なんかつけたらチャンネル回してたらたまにいて、やっぱ見た目のインパクトがすごいからさ、忘れないよ君のこと。
I don't know, but when I'd flip through channels, you'd be there sometimes. Your look has such an impact, I couldn't forget you.
あら、嬉しい。
Oh, that's nice to hear.
そうだよ。地球儀持ってるなーっていつも思ってた。
Yeah. I always thought, "He's holding a globe."
それぐらい？ 「面白いな」じゃないの？
Is that all? Not "He's funny"?
地球儀持ってるなー、あ、なんか地理詳しいのかなーって思ってた。
Just "He's holding a globe... Oh, I bet he's good at geography."
で、ちゃんと国を指差してるって。
And you were correctly pointing at countries.
あ、ちゃんと指してるよ。さっきも指したし、見せたし。
I point at them correctly. I did it just now, too.
だから、地理詳しいんだなーって思ってた。
So I thought, "He must know a lot about geography."
全然「面白い」っていうのが出てこない！
The word "funny" isn't coming out at all!
いや、面白いよ。やっぱりね、25年もやってるとね。
No, you're funny. I mean, you've been at it for 25 years.
面白いからそうやって生き残ってるんだよ。
You've survived this long because you're funny.
やっぱ、ころねちゃんがこういうこと言うことによって、ころねファンのみんながね、ゴー☆ジャスをちゃんと見てくれるようになってくる。
When Korone-chan says things like that, it makes all the Korone-fans start to take Gorgeous seriously.
そうだよ。みんな、目黒区の芸人さんをよろしく頼むよ。
That's right. Everyone, please support this comedian from Meguro Ward.
目黒区の芸人さんって…宇宙海賊のゴー☆ジャスっていうことでね。
Comedian from Meguro... I'm Gorgeous the Space Pirate, thank you very much.
宇宙海賊頼むよ。
Please support the Space Pirate.
よろしくお願いします。
Thank you for your support.
ということでね、この後も…待って、この後も？ この後も、か。
So, from here on out... Wait, is it "from here on out" or "even after this"?
いいよ。
It's fine.
この後もね、みんなの懐かしい曲がたくさん出てくるから、楽しみにしててね！
From now on, there will be lots of nostalgic songs for everyone, so please look forward to them!
お、懐かしい曲が…アルジェリア、それっ！
Oh, nostalgic songs... Algeria, there!
ここ、アルジェリア。
Here, Algeria!
あ、すごい。
Oh, amazing.
ネタ終わった？
Is the gag over?
いや、カット割りしてからのそれ、何それ？ どういういじりしてんのこれ。
Hey, reacting after the camera cut, what's with that? What kind of teasing is this?
ネタ終わった？ もういい？
Is the gag over? Are we done?
終わった、終わった。
It's over, it's over.
ゴー☆ジャスいい？
Gorgeous, are you okay?
大丈夫、大丈夫。
I'm fine, I'm fine.
もうやることない？
Nothing else to do?
やることは…コーヒー、後でコーヒー飲んどく。
What's left... Coffee. I'll drink some coffee later.
じゃ、じゃあちょっと休憩がてら、テレビでも見よう。
Well then, let's take a little break and watch some TV.
いいの、もうこんな序盤にテレビ見ちゃって。
Is it okay to watch TV this early in the show?
いいのいいの。
It's fine, it's fine.
じゃあ行こう。
Let's go.
ポチッとな。
Click!
ヤパパ ヤパパ イーシャンテン
Yapapa yapapa i-shanten
はしゃぐ恋は 池の鯉
Frolicking love is like a carp in a pond
ヤパパ ヤパパ イーシャンテン
Yapapa yapapa i-shanten
胸のタイは 抱かれたい
My heart's tie wants to be held
訳も分からずに
Without even knowing why
らんまらんまで 日が暮れる
Ranma ranma, the sun goes down
君と会ってから
Ever since I met you
らんまらんまで
Ranma ranma
なんだかんだと すったもんだの世紀末
One thing after another, a chaotic end of the century
なぜもっと静かに 「好きだよ」と言えないの?
Why can't you say "I love you" more quietly?
張り合うと私も じゃじゃ馬になっちゃう!
If we compete, I'll turn into a tomboy!
ベルも鳴らさずに
Without even ringing the bell
そよ風のように
Like a gentle breeze
胸のワンルーム
Into the studio apartment of my heart
住みついた君なの
You've come to settle in
迷惑よ だけど
It's a nuisance, but
…今夜だけいいわ
...it's okay just for tonight
（…明日までいいわ）
(...it's okay until tomorrow)
ヤパパ ヤパパ リャンシャンテン
Yapapa yapapa ryan-shanten
踊る接吻は 海の接吻
A dancing kiss is a kiss of the sea
ヤパパ ヤパパ リャンシャンテン
Yapapa yapapa ryan-shanten
恋の味は 隠し味
The taste of love is a secret ingredient
見つめられる度
Every time you look at me
らんまらんまで 目が回る
Ranma ranma, my head is spinning
恋になりそうで
It feels like love
らんまらんまで
Ranma ranma
タンマタンマで そんなもんねとお友達
Wait, wait! Let's just stay friends for now
迫力で口説かれ 星の街逃げ出した
Wooed with such intensity, I fled into the starry city
夢見てたデートが マラソンになっちゃう!
The date I dreamed of is turning into a marathon!
痒いメルヘンも
Even itchy fairy tales
乙女には媚薬
Are an aphrodisiac for a maiden
君の優しさに
In your kindness
包まれてみたいの
I want to be enveloped
冗談よ だけど
I'm just joking, but
…ハートは逃げちゃう
...my heart will run away
（…いつかは逃げちゃう）
(...someday it'll run away)
ヤパパ ヤパパ イーシャンテン
Yapapa yapapa i-shanten
はしゃぐ恋は 池の鯉。
Frolicking love is a carp in a pond.
ヤパパヤパパ・イーシャンテン。
Yapapa yapapa, ready to win.
胸のタイは 抱かれたタイ。
The sea bream in my heart wants to be held.
見つめられるたび、
Every time you look at me,
らんまらんまで 目が回る。
My head spins in a Ranma-Ranma daze.
恋になりそうで、
It feels like love,
らんまらんまで、お友達。
But in a Ranma-Ranma daze, we're just friends.
訳もわからずに、
Without knowing why,
らんまらんまで 日が暮れる。
The day ends in a Ranma-Ranma daze.
君と逢ってから、
Since I met you,
らんまらんまで、
In a Ranma-Ranma daze,
ナンダカンダと すったもんだの世紀末。
It's been one thing after another at the end of the century.
デビルマンのうた
Devilman no Uta
作詞：阿久悠 作曲：三沢郷
Lyrics: Yu Aku / Composer: Go Misawa
あれは誰だ 誰だ 誰だ
Who is that? Who is that? Who is that?
あれはデビル
That is Devil,
デビルマン デビルマン
Devilman, Devilman!
裏切り者の 名を受けて
Branded with the name of a traitor,
すべてを捨てて たたかう男
The man who threw everything away to fight.
デビルアローは 超音波
Devil Arrow is ultrasonic,
デビルイヤーは 地獄耳
Devil Ear is hell's hearing,
デビルウィングは 空をとび
Devil Wing flies through the sky,
デビルビームは 熱光線
Devil Beam is a heat ray!
悪魔の力 身につけた
Having gained the powers of a demon,
正義のヒーロー
The hero of justice,
デビルマン
Devilman,
Devilman!
はじめて知った 人の愛
Knowing human love for the first time,
そのやさしさに めざめた男
The man who awakened to that kindness.
デビルチョップは パンチ力
Devil Chop is punching power,
デビルキックは 破壊力
Devil Kick is destructive power,
デビルアイなら 透視力
Devil Eye has X-ray vision,
デビルカッターは 岩くだく
Devil Cutter crushes rocks!
悪魔の力 身につけた
Having gained the powers of a demon,
正義のヒーロー
The hero of justice,
デビルマン
Devilman,
Devilman!
あれは誰だ 誰だ 誰だ
Who is that? Who is that? Who is that?
あれはデビル
That is Devil,
デビルマン デビルマン
Devilman, Devilman!
裏切り者の 名を受けて
Branded with the name of a traitor,
すべてを捨てて たたかう男
The man who threw everything away to fight.
デビルアローは 超音波
Devil Arrow is ultrasonic,
デビルイヤーは 地獄耳
Devil Ear is hell's hearing,
デビルウィングは 空をとび
Devil Wing flies through the sky,
デビルビームは 熱光線
Devil Beam is a heat ray!
悪魔の力 身につけた
Having gained the powers of a demon,
正義のヒーロー
The hero of justice,
デビルマン
Devilman,
Devilman!
やーい、よかったねー！
Yay, that was great!
やっぱね、ころさんはね、可愛いんだよ。
I knew it, Koro-san is just so cute.
顔もそうだけどね、動きも可愛いんだよ。
Her face of course, but her movements are cute too.
全部可愛いんだよ、ゴー☆ジャス見てた？
Everything's cute. Gorgious, were you watching?
可愛いんだよねー！
She's so cute, right?!
見てた見てた！
I was watching, I was!
感動したねー。
I was moved.
めちゃめちゃ自画自賛するね。
You're really full of self-praise.
でしょー？
Right?
このね、可愛く踊れるように頑張ったんだ。
I worked really hard to dance cutely.
そうだよねー。
You did, didn't you.
いいこと言うねー、うん。
Well said. Yeah.
あれ！？
Wait!?
ちょっと待って。
Hold on a second.
何？
What is it?
ころちゃん、今どういうこと？
Koro-chan, what's going on?
二人いない今？
Are there two of you right now?
はて？
Huh?
そうだよ、ダブルころにだよ。
That's right, it's Double Koroni.
え？
What?
パペットのころちゃんと、
The puppet Koro-chan and...
本物のVのころちゃん。
...the real V-model Koro-chan.
二人いないこれ？
Are there two of you?
どういう状況これ？
What kind of situation is this?
ダブルころにだよ。
It's Double Koroni.
うわっ！ マルチバースの幕開けだ！
Whoa! It's the dawn of the multiverse!
え？ 二人でこれ喋れんの、これ？
Wait, can the two of you talk to each other?
そうだよ。
Yes, we can.
ねー、ころさーん、ねー？
Right, Koro-san? Right?
喋ってる！
They're talking!
えっ！？
What!?
ちょっと待って、ちょっとちょっと…
Wait a minute, wait wait...
二人してちょっと…
The two of you...
じゃあ、僕のちょっとあの… 「手を上げ下げゲーム」ちょっとやってもらっていい？
Well then, could you two play my 'Hands Up, Hands Down' game?
いいよ、いいよ。
Alright, alright.
せーの、右手上げて！
Ready, right hand up!
右手下ろす！
Right hand down!
左手上げないで！
Don't raise your left hand!
左手下ろす！
Left hand down!
ぐるっと回って、
Spin all the way around,
はい、ポーズ！
and pose!
いや、ちょっと違うポーズになってる！
Wait, that's a slightly different pose!
違うよ！これはだって...
No, it's not! That's because...
こっちは棒がついてるからね。
this one has a rod attached.
可動域がね、難しいんだよこれ！
The range of motion is tricky with this!
うわー、ゴージャスこれ分かるでしょ？
Whoa, Gorgeous, you see what I mean?
可動域の問題だよ！
It's a range of motion issue!
可動域の問題あったんだね。
I see, there was a range of motion issue.
そうだ、そうだ。
Right, right.
でも2倍ころね楽しめるってことでいいかな？
But does that mean we get double the Korone fun?
そうだね！
Exactly!
そうしようね、うん。
Let's go with that, yeah.
そうだ！
Oh, I know!
せっかくダブルころねもいることだしさ、
Since we have double Korone here,
スクショタイムにしない？
how about a screenshot time?
あら、いいこと言う！
Oh, that's a great idea!
パペころちゃん、いいこと言うじゃない！
Pappe-Koro-chan, that's a great idea!
でしょう？
Right?
いいこと言うよ、ゴージャスも入ってよ！
It is. Gorgeous, you join in too!
え、いいの？
Eh, really?
うん！みんなで写真撮ろうよ！
Yeah! Let's take a photo together!
撮ろう、撮ろう！
Let's do it, let's do it!
これも持とう、あ、そこに...
I'll hold this too—oh, over there...
あ、そこに着けるんだ。
Ah, you're attaching it there.
これ、持つの？
Am I holding this?
あ、ダブルころね持ちたい、それ！
Ah, Double Korone wants to hold that!
これ持ちたいの？
You want to hold this?
あ、ありがと、ありがと。
Ah, thanks, thanks.
じゃあ、一緒に持とうね。
Okay, let's hold it together.
これでいいかな？
Is this good?
はい、オッケー！
Yep, okay!
じゃあ、撮ってもらおう！
Now, let's have them take the photo!
撮っていこうか！
Let's take it!
よし、お願いします！
Alright, here we go!
準備いいよ！
Ready when you are!
うわー！小さい海坊主だ！
Whoa! It's a tiny Umibozu!
何これ？何これ？
What's this? What's this?
あ、ごめん！ころねすきーが来ちゃった、これ！
Ah, sorry! A Koronesuki showed up!
あ、これゴージャスに紹介してなかったね。
Ah, I haven't introduced them to Gorgeous.
これはうちの、あの視聴者っていうのかな？
This is one of my, what do you call them, viewers?
リスナーなんだけどさ、
A listener, basically,
ごめん、今日リスナーもいるんだよ！
sorry, the listeners are here today too!
あ、リスナーも！
Oh, the listeners too!
そう、ゴージャスに紹介しようと思って、
Yeah, I brought them along to introduce them to you,
連れてきてたの忘れてたんだ。
but I totally forgot.
びっくりした、海坊主が急にやってきたかと思った。
Scared me, I thought an Umibozu just appeared.
海坊主じゃない！ころねすきーだよ！
Not an Umibozu! It's a Koronesuki!
ほら、挨拶して！
Come on, say hello!
こんにちは。
Hello.
全然そっぽ向いてるんだけど！
He's looking in the complete opposite direction!
ちょっとあっちしか向けないんだよね、こいつね。
He can only look that way, this little guy.
そういう仕様なのね。
So it's built like that.
ゴージャス、じゃあこの子も入れてスクショいい？
Gorgeous, can we include him in the screenshot too?
スクショ撮っちゃいましょう！
Let's take it!
いい？オッケー！
Ready? Okay!
じゃあ、どういうポーズにしようかな？
Now, what pose should we do?
そこどこ？
Where's that?
これは、あの、ここの会場。
This is, uh, this venue.
言えないけど、うん。
I can't really say, but yeah.
はいポーズ！
And pose!
パシャ！
Click!
撮れたかな？
Did we get it?
いいよ。
Looking good.
あとじゃあもう一ポーズぐらい行っとく？
Shall we do one more pose?
もう一ポーズ行っとく？
One more pose?
どこ、そこ？
Where's that?
どこ行きたい？行きたい国指して！
Where do you want to go? Point to a country!
行きたいところ？
Where I want to go?
えーっと...
Uh...
目黒区！
Meguro City!
いや、同じポーズになってる！
Wait, it's the same pose again!
同じポーズだ、これ！
This is the same pose!
行くよ！せーの！
Here we go! Ready!
パシャ！
Click!
いいじゃーん！
Nice!
これは記念になりましたね！
This is quite a keepsake!
いいね、いいね！
Great, great!
じゃあ、ころねすきー、
Now, Koronesuki,
もう言うことないかな？
is there anything else you want to say?
ころねすきーに言うことある？ゴージャスは。
Gorgeous, do you have anything to say to him?
僕から？
From me?
えっと、ゴージャスも応援してね。
Uh, please support Gorgeous too.
どう、ころねすきー？
Well, Koronesuki?
何も言わない！
He's not saying anything!
ころねすきーは何も言わないわ！
Koronesuki won't say a word!
声、誰も当ててないじゃないか！
No one's even voicing him!
あ！パペころね！
Oh! Pappe-Korone!
そろそろ次の曲に行かなきゃじゃない？
Shouldn't we be moving on to the next song?
あら！
Oh my!
パペころねが！
Pappe-Korone is right!
本当だ！
You're right!
ではでは、お次の曲は...
Then, without further ado, the next song is...
ジャジャジャジャーン！
Ta-da-da-dah!
お、何これ？
Oh, what's this?
あ、ゴージャスちょっと見ててよ！
Ah, Gorgeous, check this out!
バイオリン、バイオリン、あ、それ！
Violin, violin, and up!
これバイオリン！
It's a violin!
うぉ！確かにバイオリンだ！
Whoa! It really is a violin!
ということで！
And so!
ミュージック、スタート！
Music, start!
ハニホヘトイロ、ハニホヘトイロ
Ha-ni-ho-he-to-i-ro, ha-ni-ho-he-to-i-ro
ハトイロハニホニハ、クインテット
Ha-to-i-ro-ha-ni-ho-ni-ha, Quintet
ゆうがたクインテット
Evening Quintet
夕焼け空が染まるとき
When the sunset sky starts to glow
聞こえてくるよ ゆうがたクインテット
You can hear it, the Evening Quintet
YOU GOTTA QUINTET
QUINTET QUINTET
そら元気も勇気もわいちゃうぞ
Look, energy and courage are welling up
ラララ 楽しくみんなでさわいじゃおう
La la la, let's all have fun and make some noise
涙なんかはかわいちゃう
Even tears will dry away
気がつきゃ ほら 春の夢の中
And before you know it, look, you're in a spring dream
YOU GOTTA MUSIC
MUSIC MUSIC
ゆうがたクインテット
Evening Quintet
メトロポリタン美術館
Metropolitan Museum of Art
大理石の台の上で
On top of a marble pedestal
天使の像 ささやいた
An angel statue whispered
夜になると ここは冷える
It gets chilly here at night
At night, it gets cold here.
君の服を かしてくれる？
Will you lend me your clothes?
タイムトラベルは楽し
Time travel is fun.
メトロポリタン美術館
Metropolitan Museum.
赤い靴下でよければ
If red socks are okay...
かたっぽあげる
I'll give you one.
エジプトでは ファラオ眠る
In Egypt, the Pharaoh sleeps.
石のふとんに くるまって
Wrapped in a stone futon.
呼んでみても 五千年の
Even if I try calling out...
夢を今も 見続けてる
...he's still dreaming his five-thousand-year dream.
タイムトラベルは楽し
Time travel is fun.
メトロポリタン美術館
Metropolitan Museum.
目覚まし時計 ここに
I'll set an alarm clock...
かけておくから
...right here.
バイオリンのケース
A violin case...
トランペットのケース
...a trumpet case.
トランクがわりにして
Use them as trunks...
出発だ！
...and let's depart!
タイムトラベルは楽し
Time travel is fun.
メトロポリタン美術館
Metropolitan Museum.
大好きな絵の中に
Inside my favorite painting...
とじこめられた
...I was trapped.
痛たたたたた...
Ow, ow, ow, ow, ow...
え？海？
Eh? The sea?
もしかして、さっきの絵の中に入っちゃったのかな？
Could it be that I went inside that painting?
どうしよう！
What should I do?!
おーい！ころさ〜ん！
Ohey! Koro-sa~n!
え、これはゲーマーズのみんなじゃないか、どうしたの？
Eh, isn't that everyone from Gamers? What's wrong?
溺れてるじゃん、どうしたの？ちょっとバカンスに...
You're drowning! What's wrong? On a vacation...
溺れてない、溺れてない、バカンスできてないよ。
We're not drowning, we're not drowning! We can't even vacation!
助けるよ、助けるよ！
I'll save you, I'll save you!
助けてー、助けてー！
Help us! Help us!
よいしょ！よいしょ！
Heave-ho! Heave-ho!
はあ...助かった...よかった。
Whew... we're saved... Thank goodness.
だめじゃん！
That's no good!
てかバカンスってここに誘われてないけど、なんで三人で行こうとしてるの？
Anyway, I wasn't invited to this "vacation." Why were you three trying to go?
おい...まあまあ、でもこうやって合流できたからね。そうそう。
Hey... well, we managed to meet up like this. That's right.
最終的にはよかったなって。
In the end, it's all good.
あ、そっか。お。そっかそっか。
Ah, I see. Oh. I see, I see.
じゃ、四人でバカンスに行こうか！
Then, shall the four of us go on vacation?
いっちゃおうか！いっちゃおうか！イェーイ！レッツゴー！
Shall we? Shall we? Yay! Let's go!
って、おい！
Wait, hey!
違うよ違うよ！
No, that's not it!
あれ、どうしたの？
Huh, what's wrong?
こんなのんきなこと言ってる場合じゃないんだよ。
This is no time to be so carefree!
ころたちね、絵の中に閉じ込められちゃったんだよ！
We've been trapped inside the painting!
ええええー！？
Eeeeeeh?!
え、だよね。うーん。
I know, right? Hmm.
まあ、でも大丈夫だと思うけどね。
Well, I think it'll be fine, though.
軽いな...
That's casual...
うん。なんかうちが聞いた、あの噂によると...
Yeah. According to a rumor I heard...
なんかこの海のどこかに願いをなんでも叶えてくれる宝箱があるらしいよ！
Apparently, somewhere in this sea, there's a treasure chest that can grant any wish!
ええー！？願いが叶う宝箱！？
Eeeh?! A treasure chest that grants wishes?!
まあ、ちょっとどこにあるかわかんないけどね。
Well, I don't really know where it is, though.
宝箱の力で元の世界に戻してもらえばいいんだよ！
We can just have it return us to our original world!
おーおー！すごい！
Ooh! Amazing!
じゃに、みんなで宝箱を探そう！
Then, let's all look for the treasure chest!
おー！！
Ooh!!
ひょっこりひょうたん島
Hyokkori Hyoutanjima
波をちゃぷちゃぷちゃぷちゃぷかきわけて
Splashing and parting the waves...
（チャプ チャプ チャプ）
(Chapu, chapu, chapu!)
雲をすいすいすいすい追い抜いて
Zipping and zooming past the clouds...
（スイ スイ スイ）
(Sui, sui, sui!)
ひょうたん島はどこへ行く
Where is Hyoutanjima headed?
ボクらを乗せてどこへ行く
Where is it taking us?
（うううーうううらー）
(Uru uru uraaa...)
丸い地球の水平線に
On the horizon of the round Earth...
何かがきっと待っている
Something is surely waiting.
苦しいこともあるだろさ
There might be painful times...
悲しいこともあるだろさ
And there might be sad times.
だけどボクらはくじけない
But we won't lose heart.
泣くのはいやだ 笑っちゃおう
We don't want to cry, let's just laugh.
進め！
Forward!
ひょっこりひょうたん島
Hyokkori Hyoutanjima.
Hyokkori Hyoutanjima
うわああああああ！
Whoaaa!
あ、あ、あれ？ あれ？ あれ、みんな？
Ah, a- are? Huh? Huh, everyone?
あれ、なんか... 海じゃなくなってる...
Wait, somehow... it's not the sea anymore...
あれ？ 凍っちゃったねー。 あれ？
Huh? It's frozen. Huh?
あれ？ ここはどこだ？
Huh? Where is this?
あ！ あれ？ あー！
Ah! Huh? Ah!
おー！ ちょっとスカートスカート！
Oh! Wait, my skirt, my skirt!
元に戻った！
We're back to normal!
元に戻ってるー！
戻ったんじゃー！
We returned!
じゃあ、元に戻ったということで、 はい、みおしゃ自己紹介お願いします。
Well, since we're back to normal, Mio-sha, please introduce yourself.
え？ 自己紹介から？
Eh? From the introduction?
えー、うち、うち、うちだよ。 大神ミオだよ。
Um, it's me, it's me, it's me. I'm Ookami Mio.
かわいいねー。
So cute.
はい、ホロライブゲーマーズの大神ミオです。
Yes, I'm Ookami Mio from Hololive Gamers.
次はフブキ！
Next is Fubuki!
はい！ 白上だよー！
Yes! It's Shirakami!
かわいいだろー？
Isn't it cute?
かわいいー！ はい！
Cute! Yes!
続いて...
Next up...
はーい、もぐもぐおかゆー！
Hi, Mogu Mogu Okayu!
かわいいねー。
So cute.
ホロライブゲーマーズの猫又おかゆだよー。
I'm Nekomata Okayu from Hololive Gamers.
いやー、みんなかわいいね。
Man, everyone is cute.
あ、そういえば、ころね。 6周年おめでとう！
Oh, by the way, Korone. Happy 6th anniversary!
ありがとう！
Thank you!
おめでとう！ おめでとー！
Congratulations! Congrats!
ありがとうみんな。 あれ？ なんか姿が変わってるね。
Thank you everyone. Huh? Somehow our appearance has changed.
あれ？ なんかさっきの姿と違くないか？
Huh? Isn't it different from how we looked just now?
ま、しょうがないよね、もうなんか色々...
Well, it can't be helped, you know, there's various things...
いいじゃないですか！ 細かいことは！
Isn't it fine?! Don't worry about the details!
大人の事情ね。
Adult circumstances, right.
大人の事情があるんだよ。 あ、これ皆さんね、パペットゲットしてくれてるかな？
There are adult circumstances. Oh, by the way, I wonder if everyone has gotten these puppets?
UFOキャッチャーとかで取れてたみたいだね。
It seems they were available in UFO catchers and such.
かわいいー、かわいいねー。
So cute, so cute.
え、どうだったみんな、あの、パペットでやってもらったけどさ。 楽しかった？
So, how was it everyone, doing it with puppets. Was it fun?
いや、楽しかった！ 楽しかった！
It was fun! It was fun!
すごい新鮮だったよね。
It was really fresh, wasn't it?
あんまりやんないからさ。 ちょっとみんな可愛かったよ。
We don't do this often. You were all a bit cute.
いやー、楽しかったよ。
Man, it was fun.
でもなんか、我々よりちょっと大きくなっててね。
But somehow, they became a bit bigger than us.
そう、なんかデカかった。
Yeah, they were kind of big.
そう、パクパク動いてるし。 いずれみんなもあの姿にならねーかな。
Yeah, and they're moving their mouths. I wonder if everyone will become like that eventually.
なりたいよー、かわいい！
I want to be like that, so cute!
パペットゲーマーズになろうよ。
Let's become Puppet Gamers.
いいよ、いいよ、やろうよ。 イエーイ！ パペットゲーマーズ！
Good, good, let's do it. Yay! Puppet Gamers!
ということで、運営さんお願いします。
So, staff, please.
みんなをあの姿にしてください。 お願いします。
Please make everyone look like that. Please.
お願いします。 お願いします。
Please. Please.
あと何話そっかな。
What else should we talk about?
なに？ なに？
What? What?
ころねは6周年で、なんか無いの？ 抱負とか。
Korone, it's your 6th anniversary, don't you have anything? Like aspirations.
あ、抱負？
Ah, aspirations?
6だよ、6。
It's 6, 6.
6周年やばいね。 やばいよ。
6th anniversary is crazy. It's crazy.
え、1年生が6年生になるんだよ、だって。
Eh, a first grader becomes a sixth grader, after all.
中1が高3になるんだよ、みんな。 やばくない？
A first-year junior high student becomes a third-year high school student, everyone. Isn't that crazy?
60歳が66歳になるんだよ。 やばくない？
A 60-year-old becomes a 66-year-old. Isn't that crazy?
わかるよ。 え、抱負か。
I get it. Um, aspirations...
でもさ、結構さ、デビュー時期近いじゃん。 みんな... ま、みんなは近くないか。
But you know, our debut periods are quite close. Everyone... well, maybe not everyone.
デビュー時期近いかな？
Are our debut periods close?
ころねのその数ヶ月後に、7周年だから私。
A few months after Korone's, it's my 7th anniversary.
ろく... み、7周年だわ。 あ、なっちゃうよ。
Six... mi, it's my 7th anniversary. Oh, it's becoming that.
ゲーマーズはね、デビュー時期が飛び飛びの不思議なグループなんだよ。
Gamers is a mysterious group with scattered debut periods.
ま、おかゆと近いんだけど。 じゃあ、おかゆと抱負決めたい。
Well, it's close to Okayu's. So, I want to decide on aspirations with Okayu.
あー、そうだね。 おかゆはなんかある？
Ah, that's right. Do you have anything, Okayu?
でもやっぱり、ゲーマーズは、なんかこう、すごいマイペースなのがいいじゃん。
But as expected, for Gamers, something like being very 'my pace' is good, isn't it?
だから逆にこの6周年とか、ま、フブキは7周年だけど、そういうプレッシャーに負けずに...
So on the contrary, for this 6th anniversary, or Fubuki's 7th anniversary, without losing to that kind of pressure...
いつも通りの活動を心がける、みたいな抱負でもいいんじゃあない？
Maybe an aspiration like striving for activities as usual would be good?
なるほどね。 いただきました！
I see. We've received it!
うぉ、うぉ、うぉ、うぉ！ いつも通り！ マイペースだね。
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa! As usual! 'My pace', right.
いつも通り、マイペース。 じゃあもう、毎年、マイペースでいつも通りってことじゃん。
As usual, 'my pace'. So, every year, it's just 'my pace' and as usual.
そうだよ。 何も変わらないゲーマーズってことじゃん。
That's right. It means a Gamers that never changes.
そういうことになって。 見てペラペラ。
That's how it is. Look, it's thin.
やめなペラペラ。 あ、待って。
Stop it with the 'thin'. Oh, wait.
せっかくこれパペット持ってるからさ、 ちょっと即興劇みたいなのやりたい。
Since we have these puppets, I want to do something like an improv play.
え、即興劇？！ やりたい！ うまくできるかなー？
Eh, improv?! I want to do it! I wonder if we can do it well?
大丈夫、大丈夫。 もうさ、6周年だから言うこと聞いてよ。
It's okay, it's okay. Come on, it's the 6th anniversary, so listen to what I say.
じゃあ、えーとね、じゃあ1人ずつ、ミオしゃからね、仕掛けていくやん。
Then, um, let's go one by one, starting from Mio-sha, let's set it up.
うちから？ コロネとお土産劇じゃん。
From me? It's the Korone and Souvenir play.
ぱちぱちぱち。 お腹すいたー、ミオしゃー。
Clap clap clap. I'm hungry, Mio-sha.
お、ころね、お腹空いたの？ 何か作ってあげようか。
Oh, Korone, are you hungry? Shall I make you something?
えー、いいなー。 何がいいかな？
Eh, that's nice. What would be good?
じゃあ... お前がいい！ あばばばばばばばば！！
Then... You're the one! Abababababababa!!
あ、なんか謎の力で...
Oh, by some mysterious power...
あー、うまかったうまかった。
Ah, that was tasty, tasty.
飛ばされていった...
Sent flying away...
次は、じゃあ、フブちゃん行こうか。
Next, well then, let's go with Fubuki-chan.
えっ、この流れで！？
Eh, in this flow!?
うまかったうまかった。
Tasty, tasty.
気をつけろー！
Watch out!
フブキと、ころね劇場！イェーイ！
Fubuki and Korone Theater! Yay!
ころねだころねだ。
It's Korone, it's Korone.
あ、フブちゃん、とっても美味しいレストランがあるんだけど、一緒に行かない？
Ah, Fubuki-chan, there's a very delicious restaurant, want to go together?
レストラン？え、ころねおすすめのレストランってこと！？
A restaurant? Eh, you mean Korone's recommended restaurant!?
え、行きたい行きたい！
Eh, I want to go, I want to go!
テクテクテクテク...
Teke teke teke teke...
あ、ここだよここだよ。
Ah, it's here, it's here.
わあ、素敵なレストランだね！
Wow, what a lovely restaurant!
ここのレストランはね、すごい特別な食材を使っているんだよ。
This restaurant uses a very special ingredient, you know.
特別な食材って何なに何なに！？
A special ingredient? What what what what!?
お前だよ！
It's you!
あー！フブニャー！いやだー！
Ah! Fubunyaa! Nooo!
あーはっはっはっ！
Ahahaha!
フブニャー！謎の力で...
Fubunyaa! By some mysterious power...
あ、うまかったうまかった。
Ah, that was tasty, tasty.
はい、おかゆだよ、次。
Okay, Okayu's turn next.
えー、この流れ、僕も食べられちゃうじゃん。
Ehh, in this flow, I'll be eaten too...
そんなことないよ、おかゆは特別だよ。
No way, Okayu is special.
本当にー？
Really?
じゃあ、おかゆところね劇場！
Well then, Okayu and Korone Theater!
おかころ劇場だー！イェーイ！
OkaKoro Theater! Yay!
あ、おかゆ、海に行きたくないかーい？
Ah, Okayu, don't you want to go to the sea?
海？まださ、海開きには早くない？
The sea? Isn't it a bit early for the beach season?
いいんだよ、時期の設定はいいんだよ、どうでも。
It's fine, the setting for the season doesn't matter, whatever.
え、そうなの？
Eh, is that so?
海行くよ、海！
We're going to the sea, the sea!
ハイ、ハイ、ほら海！気持ちよさそうだよ、入っておいで。
Yes, yes, look, the sea! It looks pleasant, come on in.
うー、まだ冷たいよー。入りたくないー。
Ugh, it's still cold. I don't want to go in.
大丈夫、海！行け行け行け行けー！
It's fine, the sea! Go go go go!
はい上がっておいで、上がっておいで。
Okay, come on up, come on up.
ああ、寒いよー、まだやっぱり。
Ah, it's cold, after all.
え、なんで海に入れたと思う？
Eh, why do you think I put you in the sea?
なんで海に入れたのー？
Why did you put me in the sea?
下味をつけるためだよ！アバババババ！
To season you! Om nom nom!
ああ、うまかったうまかった。ああ、うまかった。
Ah, that was tasty, tasty. Ah, that was tasty.
満足か？三人食べて。
Are you satisfied, having eaten all three?
満足。ありがとう、みんな。じゃあねー！
Satisfied. Thanks everyone, bye-bye!
「じゃあねー」じゃないだろ。
It's not 'bye-bye' yet!
寸劇ありがとうございました。
Thanks for the skit.
え、まだ歌う曲あるでしょ？
Wait, there's still a song to sing, right?
あ、そうだった！準備して！はい！
Oh, that's right! Get ready! Okay!
マッハ・ゴー・ゴー・ゴー 1997
Mach GoGoGo 1997
マッハ・ゴー・ゴー・ゴー・ゴー
Mach go, go, go, go
かぜもふるえる　ヘアピンカーブ
Kaze mo furueru hairpin curve
こわいものかと　ゴー・ゴー・ゴー
Kowai mono ka to go-go-go
ホワイトボディ　マッハごう
White body mach go
まけじだましい　おやゆずり
Makeji damashii oyayuzuri
はしりだしたら　あとにはひけぬ
Hashiridashitara ato ni wa hiken
ゆくぞしょうりの　ゴールまで
Yuku zo shouri no goal made
マッハ・ゴー・ゴー
Mach go go
マッハ・ゴー・ゴー・ゴー
Mach go go go
ちきゅうのはてまで　アクセルふんで
Chikyuu no hate made accelerator funde
わかいいのちが　ゴー・ゴー・ゴー
Wakai inochi ga go-go-go
ナンバーファイブ　マッハごう
Number five mach go
みんなみてくれ　そこから
Minna mitekure soko kara
むねにでっかい　ファイトがもえる
Mune ni dekkai fight ga moeru
とばせせいぎの　ハイウェイ
Tobase seigi no highway
マッハ・ゴー・ゴー
Mach go go
マッハ・ゴー・ゴー・ゴー
Mach go go go
うなるエンジン　みなぎるとうし
Unaru engine minagiru toushi
まけてたまるか　ゴー・ゴー・ゴー
Makete tamaru ka go-go-go
スーパーバトル　マッハごう
Super battle mach go
いくぞわがみち　どこまでも
Yuku zo waga michi doko made mo
シフトチェンジに　ちからがこもる
Shift change ni chikara ga komoru
レッドゾーンで　つきぬけろ
Red zone de tsukinukero
マッハ・ゴー・ゴー
Mach go go
マッハ・ゴー・ゴー・ゴー
Mach go go go
Hey you know what?
The rumor that you heard is true
She's back in town
Trouble "Wan"der!
Whenever wherever
We're in trouble
She will come running, Run Run!
Trouble "Wan"der!
Up & Up & Down & Down & Left & Right & Left & Right &...
Um... Let me see, what's next thing to do...
Doggy's back in Town!
sniff sniff... oh find it!
Dig here, bow wow wow
Mmm... there's nothing here!!
(Oh no)
Trouble "Wan"der!
Always spinnin' her wheels
You know only working hard...
It's just the way she is
Trouble "Wan"der!
Up & Up & Down & Down & Left & Right & Left & Right &...
Let's take a break now, take a break now
Doggy's back in Town!
Back in Back in Back in Back in Back in Town!
Doggy doggy's back in Town
Trouble "Wan"der!
Dokkin dokkin
Bakkun bakkun
Who can stop her?
Doggy doggy's back in Town! Town! Town!
Wow wow wow...
Trouble "Wan"der!
Track down a suspect
Never get caught, alright?!
Doggy, do you hear me?
(Wake up!)
Trouble "Wan"der!
Always doing her best
So she's lovable somehow
It's just the way she is
Trouble "Wan"der!
Yeah it may be sometimes she's depressed
But never never shows that side
Cuz she's a really really wonderful wonderer
No no!
She's a really Trouble "Wan"der!
Up & Up & Down & Down & Left & Right & Left & Right &...
Paw... Other Paw... Am I doing right?
Doggy's back in Town!
Back in Back in Back in Back in Back in Town!
Doggy doggy's back in Town
Trouble "Wan"der!
Dokkin dokkin
Bakkun bakkun
Who can stop her?
Doggy doggy's back in Town! Town! Town!
Wow wow wow...
Trouble "Wan"der!
Wan!
みんな、今日は見てくれてありがとう。
Everyone, thank you for watching today.
いつものころねもパペットのころねも可愛かったでしょ？
Regular Korone and puppet Korone were both cute, right?
ということで、ここでグッズ紹介です！
So, it's time for the goods introduction!
戌神ころね活動6周年記念グッズが出ます！
Inugami Korone 6th Anniversary commemoration goods are coming out!
まず初めに、ころさんのパペットシアタータペストリー！
First up, Koro-san's Puppet Theater tapestry!
今回の配信に寄せて作ってもらいました。描き下ろしはフカヒレ先生です。いつもありがとうございます。
It was made specifically for this stream. The illustration is by Fukahire-sensei. Thank you as always.
続いて、ころさんの耳カチューシャ！
Next, Koro-san's ear headband!
某遊園地で売ってる耳が好きなので作ってもらいました。
I like the ears sold at a certain amusement park, so I had these made.
続いて、ケダマころねクリップ付きぬいぐるみ！
Next, Kedama Korone plushie with clip!
これは肩に付けることもできるので、お供にしてお出かけしてください。
This can be attached to your shoulder, so please take it out with you as a companion.
続いてこちら、ころねすきークリップ付きぬいぐるみ！
Next is this, Koronesuki plushie with clip!
欲しい人がいるか分からないけど、ころねが欲しいので作ってもらいました。これもお出かけしてください。
I don't know if anyone wants it, but I wanted it, so I had it made. Take this out too.
全部買った方にはステッカーと、ころね...あ、ころねすきーへの感謝の言葉ボイスがつきますよ。
For those who buy everything, you'll get a sticker and a "words of gratitude to Koronesuki" voice pack.
発売は9時からとなっております。よろしくね。
Sales start at 9:00. Please check them out.
ゴージャス。
Gorgeous.
ごめん、お待たせ。
Sorry to keep you waiting.
いやいや。お待たせ、ごめんごめん。
No, no. Sorry for keeping you waiting.
いやー。
Wow.
終わった、終わった。
It's over, it's over.
終わった。
It's over.
お待たせね。
Sorry to keep you waiting.
いっぱいグッズ出すんだね。
You're releasing a lot of merch, aren't you?
うん、いっぱいそうだよ。
Yeah, it looks like it.
いやー、いいな。
Wow, that's nice.
めっちゃ儲かっちゃって。
You must be making a killing.
そうだよ。お金がガッポガッポ。
That's right. The money's rolling in.
いや、すごいこと言う。すごいこと言う。
Wow, you say such things. You say such things.
やめてよ、そういうこと言うから。
Stop it, you're the one saying it.
ごめんごめん、ごめんよ。うん。
Sorry, sorry, my bad. Yeah.
で、ゴージャスのさ、年収はいくらなの？つって。
So, Gorgeous, what's your annual income? Just wondering.
えっとね、100万ギャラクシー。
Well, it's 1 million Galaxy.
いくらかわかんない。
I don't know how much that is.
そうそうそう、そうしとこ。そうしとこ。うん。
Right, right, let's go with that. Let's go with that. Yeah.
で、ゴージャスは今日どうだった？
So, Gorgeous, how was today for you?
いや、ちょっとね、ころちゃんと初めましてで。
Well, it was my first time meeting Koro-chan.
結構仲良くなれてね。
And we got along pretty well.
そうだよね。
We did, didn't we?
ね。ちょっとこれからなんかコラボとかもやっていけたらいいなと思ってる。
Yeah. I'm hoping we can do some collabs and stuff from now on.
いいじゃん。コラボレボリューションじゃん。
Sounds good. A collab revolution.
コラボ・コラボ・レボリューション！
Collab, collab, revolution!
いや、ちょっとまだ合ってないね。
Wait, we're not quite in sync yet.
まだこれからだね。
It's still early days.
これから、これからね。詰めていこう。うん。
From now on, from now on. Let's work on it. Yeah.
え、なんかゴージャスはなんかいいの？言うことあったらいいよ。
Hey, Gorgeous, is there anything else? If you have something to say, go ahead.
じゃあ、告知みたいな感じ？
So, like an announcement?
ああ、いいよいいよ。使って使って。
Oh, sure, go ahead. Use this time.
えー、ゴージャス、えー、2024年、2025年にかけて、そろそろ...
Well, Gorgeous, through 2024 and 2025, it's about time...
ああ！
Ah!
オッケー。
Okay.
ああ、神様が。
Ah, God is...
うん、終われってね。
Yeah, telling you to wrap it up.
神様がね。
God, huh.
助かったーって思ってるところもある、ちょっと。
Part of me feels relieved, actually.
うん、あ、そうなの？
Oh, really?
わかった。じゃあさ。
I see. Well then.
見てる人たちにバイバイしようか。
Should we say goodbye to the viewers?
オッケー。バイバイしよう。
Okay. Let's say goodbye.
うん。
Yeah.
せーの！
Ready, set...
バイバイー！
Bye-bye!
戌神ころね 6周年記念ライブ
Inugami Korone 6th Anniversary Live
それでは聴いてください。
Now, please listen to this song.
戌神ころねで...
By Inugami Korone...
『ころねのさにーでい！』
“Korone's Sunny Day!”
ゆびゆびゆびゆび　ゆびだせよー
Yubi yubi yubi yubi, give me your fingers!
ゆびゆびゆびゆび　ゆびゆびゆびゆび
Yubi yubi yubi yubi, yubi yubi yubi yubi
おなかがすいたら　ころねびいき
If you're hungry, you're a Korone fan
おててのしわとしわをあわせて
Put your hands together, palm to palm
しあわせ　なむー！
Happiness, Namu-!
はい！ はい！ はい！ はい！
Hai! Hai! Hai! Hai!
わんわん！ わんわん！
Wan wan! Wan wan!
みんなで一緒に！
Everyone together!
はい！
Hai!
ゆびゆび！
Yubi yubi!